[
  {
    "Question": "In CSS, Flex is a shorthand property for which of the following properties?",
    "Difficulty": "medium",
    "Answer": "flex-grow, flex-shrink, and flex-basis",
    "Distractor1": "justify-content, align-items, and align-content",
    "Distractor2": "flex-direction, flex-wrap, and flex-flow",
    "Distractor3": "flex-direction, order, and flex-flow"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which CSS property is used to represent the transparency of an element?",
    "Difficulty": "easy",
    "Answer": "Opacity",
    "Distractor1": "Dark",
    "Distractor2": "Transparent",
    "Distractor3": "Hover"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following CSS properties represents the order of flex items in a container?",
    "Difficulty": "medium",
    "Answer": "order",
    "Distractor1": "float",
    "Distractor2": "overflow",
    "Distractor3": "int"
  },
  {
    "Question": "In HTML, which of the following is the correct way for showing how to import an external script?",
    "Difficulty": "easy",
    "Answer": "<script src='index.js'></script>",
    "Distractor1": "<script add='index.js'></script>",
    "Distractor2": "<script adding-js='index.js'></script>",
    "Distractor3": "<script js='index.js'></script>"
  },
  {
    "Question": "In HTML, which element is used to insert a favicon?",
    "Difficulty": "medium",
    "Answer": "link element",
    "Distractor1": "fav element",
    "Distractor2": "favicon element",
    "Distractor3": "icon element"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is the correct way of creating an anchor element in HTML?",
    "Difficulty": "easy",
    "Answer": "<a href= 'www.freecodecamp.org'> freeCodeCamp </a>",
    "Distractor1": "<a>www.freecodecamp.org <freeCodeCamp /a>",
    "Distractor2": "<a href='www.freecodecamp.org' freeCodeCamp /a>",
    "Distractor3": "<a 'link'='www.freecodecamp.org' freeCodeCamp > </a>"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is meant by an empty tag in HTML?",
    "Difficulty": "medium",
    "Answer": "An empty tag doesn't require a closing tag",
    "Distractor1": "There is no such concept of empty tag in HTML",
    "Distractor2": "An empty tag cannot having any content within it",
    "Distractor3": "None of these"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which HTML element is used to 'link' to a 3rd party JavaScript library and make it available on your page?",
    "Difficulty": "medium",
    "Answer": "<script>",
    "Distractor1": "<input>",
    "Distractor2": "<head>",
    "Distractor3": "<html>"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How many Section Heading elements are there in HTML5?",
    "Difficulty": "easy",
    "Answer": "6",
    "Distractor1": "4",
    "Distractor2": "8",
    "Distractor3": "1"
  },
  {
    "Question": "In JavaScript, if let x='Prakhar', then what will be the result for console.log(x.substring(2,5))?",
    "Difficulty": "hard",
    "Answer": "akh",
    "Distractor1": "akaha",
    "Distractor2": "aka",
    "Distractor3": "akkkaha"
  },
  {
    "Question": "In JavaScript, what is the range of numbers returned from the Math.random() method?",
    "Difficulty": "hard",
    "Answer": "Between 0 and 1 (including 0; not including 1).",
    "Distractor1": "Between 0 and 1 (including neither 0 or 1).",
    "Distractor2": "Between 0 and 1 (including 1; not including 0).",
    "Distractor3": "Between 0 and 100 (including 0; not including 100)."
  },
  {
    "Question": "In JavaScript, what is the difference between the indexOf() and search() methods?",
    "Difficulty": "medium",
    "Answer": "indexOf() can take a second parameter while search() cannot",
    "Distractor1": "Both methods are the same",
    "Distractor2": "indexOf() only takes regular expressions",
    "Distractor3": "The search() method runs 4x faster than the indexOf() method"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What does the 'debugger' statement in JavaScript do?",
    "Difficulty": "hard",
    "Answer": "It acts as a breakpoint in a program",
    "Distractor1": "It will debug errors in the current statement",
    "Distractor2": "It will debug all the errors in the program at runtime",
    "Distractor3": "All of the above"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What kind of programming can JavaScript be used for?",
    "Difficulty": "medium",
    "Answer": "Both Client and Server side programming",
    "Distractor1": "Server side only",
    "Distractor2": "Client side only",
    "Distractor3": "None of these options"
  },
  {
    "Question": "In JavaScript, if let x='5', then what will be the value of console.log(x==5,x===5)?",
    "Difficulty": "medium",
    "Answer": "true false",
    "Distractor1": "true true",
    "Distractor2": "false true",
    "Distractor3": "false false"
  },
  {
    "Question": "In JavaScript, which Web API is used to display a dialog box with an optional message?",
    "Difficulty": "medium",
    "Answer": "window.alert()",
    "Distractor1": "window.alertHTML()",
    "Distractor2": "window.alertContent()",
    "Distractor3": "window.alertBox()"
  },
  {
    "Question": "In JavaScript, if let word='Intelligent', then what will be the value of word.slice(2,5)?",
    "Difficulty": "medium",
    "Answer": "tel",
    "Distractor1": "tellig",
    "Distractor2": "ll",
    "Distractor3": "Inigent"
  },
  {
    "Question": "In Javascript, what keyword is used to check whether a given property in an object is valid?",
    "Difficulty": "hard",
    "Answer": "in",
    "Distractor1": "is in",
    "Distractor2": "exists",
    "Distractor3": "lies"
  },
  {
    "Question":  "What is the name of the international body responsible for establishing the most common web accessibility standards?",
    "Difficulty": "hard",
    "Answer": "World Wide Web Consortium(W3C)",
    "Distractor1": "Websites for All",
    "Distractor2": "Web Accessibility Initiative (WAI)",
    "Distractor3": "A11y"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why is it important to use semantic elements when writing HTML?",
    "Difficulty": "medium",
    "Answer": "Semantic code clearly describes the code's meaning to both the browser and the developer",
    "Distractor1": "Semantic code is prettier.",
    "Distractor2": "Semantic code decreases site readability.",
    "Distractor3": "Semantic code can improve comprehension for hearing-impaired individuals."
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which one is the correct HTML element used to identify the main language of an entire page?",
    "Difficulty": "medium",
    "Answer": "<html>",
    "Distractor1": "<!DOCTYPE>",
    "Distractor2": "<body>",
    "Distractor3": "<img>"
  },
  {
    "Question": "In Git, how can you stage a file that ends with a *.txt extension?",
    "Difficulty": "medium",
    "Answer": "git add *.txt",
    "Distractor1": "git add *.text",
    "Distractor2": "git add -a .txt",
    "Distractor3": "git add - *.txt"
  },
  {
    "Question": "In Git, how can you save uncommitted changes on your local machine so you can work on it later?",
    "Difficulty": "hard",
    "Answer": "git stash",
    "Distractor1": "git copy into notepad.exe",
    "Distractor2": "git save code",
    "Distractor3": "git clone --for later"
  },
  {
    "Question": "In Git, how can you check your configuration?",
    "Difficulty": "hard",
    "Answer": "git config -l",
    "Distractor1": "git config -check",
    "Distractor2": "git checkconfig -l",
    "Distractor3": "git checkconfig -m"
  }
]